德威特先生:西维尔先生,西维尔太太,请坐你们通常的位置.
Mr.Dewitt: Mr.and Mrs.Seaver.Please, take your usual seats.So, doctor Seaver.
那么,西维尔医生,精神病学界怎么样呀?
How's the world of psychiatry?
杰森:好,好.那么本怎么样?
Jason: Fine.Fine.So what about Ben?
德威特先生:西维尔太太,我真喜欢看你19频道的新闻广播.
Mr.Dewitt: And Mars Seaver.Gee I miss your newscasts on channel nineteen.
你为什么离开了?
Why did you leave?
麦琪:德威特先生,我们可以回到正题吗?
Maggie: Mr.Dewitt, could we please get to the point?
德威特先生:对不起,我闲聊了.我相信现在轮到你们了.
Mr.Dewitt: well excuse me for making small talk.Now I believe it's your turn.
杰森:哦,那么,德威特先生,你的妻子好吗?
Jason: Oh, so, how is the wife Mr.Dewitt?
德威特先生:已经离婚了.这是我一生中非常痛苦时期,
Mr.Dewitt: Getting divorced.
我不敢相信你提起了这件事.
It's a very painful time in my life and I can't believe you brought it up.
麦琪:德威特先生,本出了什么事?
Maggie: Mr.Dewitt, what is the problem with Ben?
德威特先生:哦,他被停学了.
Mr.Dewitt: Oh, he's suspended.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
德威特先生:在前段时间,
Mr.Dewitt: During forth period, Janitor Bob spotted him at the mall.
门卫鲍勃看见他在"你那里"的厕所走廊发呆.
At Leylanni's Loo Aisle on a stick.
杰森:那所有的女招待都穿三点式?
Jason: That's where all the counter girls wear the coconut bras?
德威特先生:现在,你已经听说了?
Mr.Dewitt: Now, you've heard of it?
杰森:不,不,
Jason: No, no I haven't.
我不知道.而且逃课是很严重的,但是这是否非停学不可.
And skipping class is serious, but is it worth a suspension?
德威特先生:不.但是问题在这.
Mr.Dewitt: No.But this is.
当我叫本.西维尔来我办公室时,一个中国男孩去了.
When I had Ben Seaver sent to my office, a young Chinese boy arrives.
麦琪:哦,在这个学校还有另外一个本.西维尔?
Maggie: Oh, there is another Ben Seaver in the school?
德威特先生:事实上,最新统计,有六个本.西维尔.在上英语,西班牙语,自然,以及体育,代数和购物.
Mr.Dewitt: As a matter of fact, last count, there were six Ben savers.Covering; English, Spanish, Science, Physical Education, Algebra and Shot.
杰森:那么他没有上任何这些课程?
Jason: So he hasn't been attending any of those classes?
德威特先生:不仅这学期.但是比较有趣的是,你的成绩却从来没有好过.
Mr.Dewitt: Not this semester.And the funny part is, he's never done better.
德威特先生:大家注意了.我是德威特校长.本.西维尔,我要你不等话筒上我的唾沫干,就到我的办公室里来.
Mr.Dewitt: Attention people.This is Principle Dewitt.Ben Seaver, I want to see you in my office before the spittle dries on this microphone.
本:伙计们.嗨,伙计们,等一下.这次我自己去.我已经吃过午饭了.
Ben: Guys.Hey guys wait up.I'll take this one.I'm back from lunch.
麦琪:本 西维尔,你怎么这么做?
Maggie: Ben Seaver, how could you do this?
本:对不起,妈妈.
Bens: I'm sorry mum.
杰森:尔不要出来,年轻人,直到我告诉你动.嗨,你还动了.
Jason: And don't come out young man until I tell you to move.Hey you moved.
本:我呼吸.
Ben: I breathed.
杰森:那么保持最小动作.
Jason: Well keep it to a minimum.
麦琪:杰森,他为什么会这样?为什么他要逃学三个月?
Maggie: Jason, why would he do this?Why would he skip school for three months?
杰森:我不知道.
Jason: I don't know.
麦琪:记得他曾经是很爱上学的.
Maggie: Remember when he used to just love going to school?
杰森:不.从来没有.
Jason: No.He never did.
麦琪:确信他喜欢过.尽管是低年级.
Maggie: Well sure he did.All through the early grades.
站森:亲爱的,我所知道的是,
Jason: Honey, all I know is that when you went back to work and I was
你上班后,我开车带他去上学,我得从车里把他往外拽.
driving him, I had it drag him out of the car.
麦琪:那么你是说,因为我是个职业母亲导致这一切的?
Maggie: So you are saying that my being a working mother caused all this?
杰森:不,小甜心.别那么荒谬了.你的职业持续了什么,三年了?
Jason: No sweetheart.Don't be ridiculous.Your career lasted what, three years?
开萝尔:这是正式的,本.你现在是个完全的失败者.
Carol: It's official Ben.You are now a total loser.
本:开萝尔,为什么你不拔掉你脸上的毛?
Ben: Carol, why don't you go pluck those hairs off your face?
迈克:嗨.
Mike: Hey.
本:迈克,猜猜谁得到两周的假期?
Ben: Mike, guess who's got a two week vacation?
迈克:呃,让我猜猜,是不是他又高又笨?
Mike: Uh let me guess, is he tall and goofy?
本:无论无何他是高.
Ben: Well he's tall anyway.
迈克:嗨!
Mike: Hey!
开萝尔 :我真不能相信,你被停了学还这么高兴.
Carol: I can't believe you are so proud that you got suspended.
本:迈克:把这事跟她解释一下.
Ben: Mike, explain it to her.
迈克:喔喔喔.你被停学了?
Mike: Woo woo wo.You got suspended?
本:大呼小叫的.而且学校整个少数派淘气俱乐部都支持我.
Ben: Yipper dipper.And I took the whole Drea Himer naughty club with me.
迈克:啊,本,本.这可不好.
Mike: Ah Ben, Ben.This is not good.
本:为什么不好?
Ben: Why not?
迈克:因为这样一来,我就又要因为这被责怪了.
Mike: Because some how I am going to be blamed for this.
开萝尔:我知道这一天会到来.
Carol: I knew this day was coming.
我意思是说,你可以一直另人厌恶,
I mean you could only be repulsive for so long and then the world just
然后这世界就会把你抛弃.
vomits you out.
杰森:好了,各位.我们需要和本谈谈.
Jason: Ok everybody.We want to talk to Ben.
开萝尔:过来,克莉丝.我给你讲个故事.
Carol: Come on Chrissy.I'll tell you a story.
克莉丝:什么故事?
Chrissy: What story?
开萝尔:那么,故事叫没有脑袋的男孩.
Carol: Well, it's called the boy with no brain.
杰森:好了,本,第一:不允许看电视.
Jason: Alright Ben, number one: no TV.
本:永远?
Ben: Ever?
杰森:永远.
Jason: Ever.
本:那么如果有自然灾害,
Ben: Well what if there's a natural disaster and I have to turn it on
我不得不打开电视来得到进一步的指示?
for further instructions?
杰森:你会死的.
Jason: You'll die.
麦琪:杰森,我来处理这事.
Maggie: Jason, I was going to handle this.
本:好的,爸爸.让我们听听妈妈有什么观点.
Ben: Yeah dad.Let's hear what's on mums mind.
麦琪:本,
Maggie: Ben, we are going to go over every class you skipped.
我们需要复习你逃的每一节课.在两星期之内你必须赶上别人,
You are going to catch up in these two weeks even if you have to study
哪怕你不得不每天学习24小时.
twenty four hours a day.
本:爸爸,你说说看?
Ben: Dad, you were saying?
杰森:那么,本,
Jason: Well Ben, there's always boarding school.
通常会有寄宿学校.你知道,在那儿每天早上6点起床,
You know, where your day begins at six am with a nice brisk ten mile run
然后跑上10英里的路,接着再上8,
and then it's off to classes for eight or nine hours.
9小时的课,在寄宿学校,你不会逃课.
You don't skip classes in boarding school.
否则没有幽默感的胖女人带着狗会一直追你,直到抓住.
Otherwise large women with no sense of humour hunt you down with dogs.
杰森:什么这么有趣,小甜心?
Jason: What's so funny sweetheart?
克莉丝:电视里.每个人都需要钱.
Chrissy: The Farside.Everybody does it with Rhinos.
杰森:在用词上需要帮助吗?
Jason: Need any help with words?
克莉丝:我看起来像本吗?
Chrissy: Do I look like Ben?
麦琪:够了,克莉丝.
Maggie: That is quite enough Chrissy.
开萝尔:各位早上好,评论版,请给我.
Carol: Good morning all.The editorial page please.
杰森:你看吧.
Jason: There you go.
克莉丝:什么叫做评论版?
Chrissy: What is an editorial page?
开萝尔:这上面有人们对重要问题发表的看法.等你长大了,
Carol: Well it's where opinions are voiced on important issues.
你就会看的.
When you get older you'll be reading it.
等本长大了,他会在它下面睡觉的.
And when Ben gets older, he'll be sleeping under it.
麦琪:我想在本到这里之前,最好每个人都离开了.
Maggie: I think it would be nice if everyone left before Ben gets here.
开萝尔:我想要离开.我甚至不愿意看见他.
Carol: well I'd love to leave.I can_t even look at him.
麦琪:你知道,有好长时间没这样了,就我们俩待在家里.
Maggie: You know it has been a long time since just the two of us have been at home together.
本:是的.
Ben: Yeah.
麦琪:记得你以前每天都这样.
Maggie: Remember when it used to be like this every day?
本:是的,然后你回去工作了.
Ben: Sure, then you went back to work.
麦琪:那使你烦恼?
Maggie: That bothered you?
本:没关系.
Ben: Doesn't matter.
麦琪:啊,我没有这样认为.
Maggie: Uh, I didn't think so.
本:但是你为了克莉丝,你又回家了.
Ben: But you did come home for Chrissy though.
麦琪:亲爱的,如果我知道你会变成这样,
Maggie: Honey, if I knew you were going to turn out like this,
我绝不会回去工作的.
I never would have gone back to work.
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thanks.
麦琪:不,不.
Maggie: No, no.Ben,
本,我想每天我先给你10分钟的自由时间.
I figured we'd start each day with a ten minute free period.You can think.
你可以想.你可以说话.
You can talk.You can ask me anything and maybe we get to know each other
你可以问我任何问题,而且也许我们能更加了解对方你可以做任何你想做的.
better.You can do whatever you want.
本:好极了.
Ben: Great.
麦琪:好.那么你在读什么?
Maggie: Right.So what are you reading?
本:尼克斯队输了.
Ben: The Nicks lost.
麦琪:恩,因为湖人队很强,当魔术师正处在最佳状态.
Maggie: Hmm, well the Lakers are pretty strong when Magic is on his game.
本:你知道魔术师约翰逊为湖人队效力?
Ben: You knew Magic Johnson played for the Lakers?
麦琪:哦,是的.当他在密西根州时,我就是他的球迷了.
Maggie: Oh yeah, I've been following him since he was at Michigan state.
那是所大学,本.那么,文章说了些什么?
That's a college Ben.So, what does the article say?
本:尼克斯真糟.
Ben: The Nicks blew.
麦琪:但是作者是用什么词来表达这个意思的.
Maggie: But what word does the writer use to convey that thought?
本:他用了一团糟.
Ben: He used the word blew.
尼克斯队的一团糟像从泰式饭店出来的废气一样.
The Nicks blew like the exhaust from a Thai restaurant.
麦琪:这就叫做明喻.
Maggie: That's called a simile.
本:什么?
Ben: A what?
麦琪:明喻.也就是直截了当的打比方.现在,你说一个.
Maggie: A simile.It's a figure of speech used as a comparison.Now you try one.
本:我不懂,妈妈.我笨得像电线杆.
Ben: I don't know mum.I'm as dumb as a post.
麦琪:很好.
Maggie: Right.
本:什么?
Ben: What?
麦琪:笨得像电线杆.这又是一个明喻.
Maggie: Dumb as a post.That's another simile.
本:是的?
Ben: Yeah?
麦琪:是的.埃维抢到多少篮板球?
Maggie: Yeah.And how many rebounds did Ewing get?
本:恩,防守10个,进攻8个.
Ben: Um, ten defensive, eight offensive.
麦琪:那么加起来?
Maggie: And that makes?
本:18个.
Ben: Eighteen.
麦琪:还有比赛在哪儿进行的?
Maggie: And the game was played in?
本:洛杉矶.
Ben: Los Angeles.
麦琪:在什么地方?
Maggie: Which is in?
本:呃.
Ben: Urrrr.
麦琪:那是在影视巨星住的地方
Maggie: It's where all the big movie stars live.
本:贝蒂 福特诊所?
Ben: The Betty Ford clinic?
麦琪:在哪?
Maggie: Which is in?
本:加州.
Ben: California.
麦琪:对了,本,你刚才已经学了英语,数学,
Maggie: Right.Ben you have just studied English math geography and health.
地理和卫生.瞧,你能行的.
See, you can do it.
本:妈妈,这句是不是明喻:开萝尔是个丑陋的屁股?
Ben: Mum, would this be a simile: Carol is butt ugly?
歌曲:星期一早晨去上学.老师教黄金法则.美国历史和应用数学.你学习刻苦打开咖啡?飞快的写字.在你身后的小子不会让你单独流下.铃声响.在食堂里的午饭准备被倒掉.如果你幸运,你可以找到位置.回到教室,打开课本.老师不知道她看起来有多丑陋.不久铃声响起.你发现一天结束.
Song: Monday morning and out to school.The teacher is teaching the golden rule.American
history and practical math.You studying hard to open the caf?
Working your fingers right
down to the bone.The guy behind you won't leave you alone.Ring ring goes
the bell.The cook in the lunch room is ready to fail.You are lucky
if you can find a seat.Back in the classroom open your books.The teacher
don't know how mean she looks.Soon three o clock rolls around.You find the
day is over
本:哇.瞧瞧所有那些东西到处爬.
Ben: Wow.look at all those things crawling around.
麦琪:他们叫作微生物.
Maggie: They are called micro organisms.
本:而且他们都生活在我的一口吐沫里?
Ben: And they all live in the wad of my spit?
麦琪:对的.
Maggie: That's right.
本:哇.这样的话,我要再三考虑是否咽口水了,是吗?
Ben: Wow.Kind of makes you think twice about swallowing, doesn't it.
麦琪:想象你吻女孩子会发生什么.
Maggie: Imagine what happens when you kiss a girl.
本:是呀,那……妈妈!
Ben: Yeah, that...mum!
麦琪:哦,午饭时间.你获得另外的10分钟自由时间.
Maggie: Oh lunch time.You get another ten minute free period.
本:这些你都从哪儿学来的,妈妈?
Ben: Where did you learn all this stuff Mum?
麦琪:大学里.
Maggie: In college.
本:你上大学了?
Ben: You went to college?
麦琪:哦,你认为是什么?你以为是我全部是编出来的.
Maggie: Oh what did you think?You think I was making all this up?
本:我不确定.
Ben: I wasn't sure.
麦琪:那么我没有编.
Maggie: Well I'm not.
本:那么我怎么才能再使用这些东西,例如我的吐沫莉有什么,
Ben: Well how can I reuse something like what's in my spit,
或者马萨诸塞州在哪?
or where Massachusetts is?
麦琪:这样,如果说你想要参加凯尔特语比赛.
Maggie: Well, let's say you wanted to go to a Celtics game.
如果不知道马萨诸塞州,你甚至不会获得比赛机会.
Without Massachusetts, you don't stand much of a chance.
本:那么,那也可能在宾夕法尼亚州的费城的路上举行,
Ben: Well, they could be on the road in Philadelphia which is in
或者是科罗拉多州的丹佛,或伊利诺斯州的芝加哥.
Pennsylvania, or Denver which is Colorado, or Chicago which is in Illinois.
麦琪:本,我相信你在学习.
Maggie: Ben, I do believe you are learning.
本:而且我得到了美妙线条的屁股.
Ben: And I am getting a nice trim fanny.
麦琪:亲爱的,对不起,我有的只是简.方单的磁带.
Maggie: Honey, I'm so sorry that all I have is Jane Fonda tapes.
本:很好,妈妈.事实上,我十分喜欢看那些女人穿紧身……午饭吃什么?
Ben: That's ok mum.Actually, I kind of like watching all those women in tight
What's for lunch
麦琪:嗨,亲爱的,今天怎么样?
Maggie: Hi honey, how was your day?
杰森:那么,人们不能自控已经在一个令人担忧的比率,
Jason: Well, people are losing their minds at an alarming rate,
这样会让我们成功.
which leaves us sitting pretty.
麦琪:瞧这个.
Maggie: Look at this.
杰森:那是什么?
Jason: What's that?
麦琪:我给本一个测试来看看过去两个星期他学到了什么,
Maggie: I gave Ben a test to see what he's learnt these past two weeks
而且他每门课都通过了.
and he passed every course.
杰森:开萝尔跟屁股一样丑陋?
Jason: Carol's as ugly as a butt?
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,我真为他骄傲.
Maggie: Oh honey, I am so proud of him.
你真该去看看他,他事实上喜欢读书的,
You should see him and he's actually enjoying learning and we are getting
而且我们相处得非常融洽,抱歉,我太激动了.
along so well and I'm sorry I'm gushing.
杰森:激动,激动!
Jason: Gush, gush!
克莉丝:嗨,妈妈.嗨,爸爸.再见,妈妈.再见,爸爸.
Chrissy: Hi mum.Hi dad.Bye mum.Bye dad.
杰森:是我,还是克莉丝身上发出一股烤肉的味道?
Jason: Is it me or is Chrissy starting to smell like roast pork?
麦琪:克莉丝,你衣服里面是什么?
Maggie: Chrissy, what do you have under your jacket?
克莉丝:这不是我的主意.沃特对我说,
Chrissy: It wasn't my idea.Veto said Ben's got to have this.
本要吃这个.本已经两个星期没吃了,现在一定快疯了.
He's gone two weeks without it and he must be going crazy by now.
杰森:克莉丝,快回你屋里去.
Jason: Chrissy go to your room.
进一步考虑,先坐到门口让这股味散掉.
On second thought, go sit on the front porch and air out.
麦琪:那是什么?
Maggie: What's that?
杰森:这是"你那里"的丁香烤肉串.亲爱的,
Jason: Leylanni cloven hoof special.Honey, she's right next to my barber.
她就在我理发师隔壁.瞧,还有张油腻腻的纸条.
Look, there is a greasy note in there.
麦琪:本,长长的噩梦结束了.
Maggie: Ben, the long nightmare is over.
星期一购物课后在"你那里"店见.签名的是沃特和敢死队.
See you at leylanni's on Monday for shop class.
我在开自己的玩笑,
Signed veto and the coconut boys.I was kidding myself Jason.
杰森.那学校他一天都不能待.
He won't last a day in that school.
杰森:哦,行了,
Jason: Oh come on honey.Just a minute ago you were gushing.
亲爱的.一分钟前,你还激动呢.
You don't know if he's going to revert to his old ways.
你不知道如果他恢复他以前的方式.也许你已经给予他力量来抵抗这种诱惑.
Maybe you've given him the strength to resist that kind of temptation.
本:嘿,妈妈,我想和你谈谈……行."你那里"的丁香烤肉串.哦,对,是"你那里"开着破车亲自送来的吗?
Ben: Hey mum, I wanted to talk to you ......alright.Leylanni's clove hoof special.Oh
yeah.Did Leylanni deliver em herself with her wicky wicky wagon
麦琪:哦!
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:恩.
Jason: Hm hm.
麦琪:哦!
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:恩.
Jason: Hm Hm.
麦琪:哦!
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:是的,是的,什么呀?
Jason: Yeah yeah what?
麦琪:哦,我可以在家里教本.
Maggie: Oh I can teach Ben at home.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:亲爱的,不必把他送回那敢死队,
Maggie: Honey we don't have to send him back to the coconut boys and who
谁知道会发生什么事情.
knows what on a stick.
杰森:亲爱的,你不是老师.
Jason: Honey, you are not a teacher.
麦琪:不,不,
Maggie: No, no, Jason.
杰森.我教了他两星期,他做的比他在几周学的都好.
I was for two weeks and he's done better than he has in weeks.
杰森:但是我相信其中有些法律问题.
Jason: But I'm sure there are some legalities,
麦琪:所以我们请个律师.我只是说这学期只剩的时间.
Maggie: So we'll get a lawyer.
我只是,
I'm just talking about for the rest of the semester.
杰森,
I Just, Jason I just want Ben to know how really good he is and that
我只是要让本知道他很聪明,他并不是个笨蛋.
he's not a dummy.
杰森:但是上学学的东西要比理论知识多的多,麦琪.有社会活动.
Jason: Well there's a lot more to school than the academics Maggie.There is socialization
麦琪:哦,社会活动!
Maggie: Oh, socialization!Is that what you call three guys starring at
就是三个小子盯着穿比基尼的姑娘看?
a girl in a coconut bikini?
杰森:那是我成长的阶段.
Jason: Was when I was growing up.
麦琪:杰森,现在本需要集中精力学习.
Maggie: Jason, right now Ben needs to focus on learning.
如果现在不开始认真的话,他就永远赶不上了.
He could be lost forever if he doesn't start now.
杰森:亲爱的,教他两个星期,
Janson: Honey, its a lot different teaching for two weeks than teaching
和教他两个月是完全不同的.
for two months.
麦琪:那就是我所指望的了,杰森.
Maggie: Well that's what I'm counting on Jason.
我想在他身旁帮助他,我没有……之前.
I mean I want to be there for him like I wasn't...before.
杰森:你真的相信这点,是吗?
Jason: You really believe in this don't you?
麦琪:杰森,这两个星期,
Maggie: Jason, we've gotten so close in the last two weeks.
我和他相处得好极了.我只是,我只是不想失去这种关系.
I just, I just don't want to lose that.
杰森:可是本指望着明天重回学校呢?
Jason: Well Ben's counting on going back to school tomorrow.
麦琪:那样,早饭的时候,
Maggie: Wwell I'll tell him at breakfast tomorrow.
我会告诉他的.他没吃饱的时候还容易对付.
He's easier to handle before he's been fed.
克莉丝:哇!你怎么穿这么好去上学?
Chrissy: Wo!How come you are wearing good clothes for school?
本:因为我所有的脏衣服都脏了.
Ben: Cos all my dirty clothes are dirty.
克莉丝:没关系的.我第一天上学也很紧张.
Chrissy: It's ok.I was nervous my first day too.
本:嘿,我没紧张.
Ben: Hey, I'm not nervous.
克莉丝:为什么卡通片还没开始,你就起来了?
Chrissy: Then how come you re up before the good cartoons are on?
本:嗨,让我单独一个人.行吗.
Ben: Hey, leave me alone.Ok.
克莉丝:紧张.非常紧张.
Chrissy: Nervous.Very nervous.
本:对呀.我不能穿这个上学,这是件烂衣服.
Ben: Yeah.I can't wear this to school, this is weenie junk.
麦琪:本,你起的真早,而且穿的就像一个小绅士.
Maggie: Ben, you are up early and you are dressed like such a little gentleman.
本:瞧,妈妈,我得换件衣服去上学.
Ben: Look mum, I got to go change for school.
麦琪:本,啊,我想跟你谈谈上学的事.
Maggie: Ben, uh, I wanted to talk to you about school.
本:那怎么了?
Ben: Well what about it?
麦琪:本,你这两星期所学到的东西,真让我感到自豪.你会觉得怎么样,
Maggie: Ben, what you have learned in these two weeks has made me so proud.
如果,啊,你没有必要去上学?
What would you say if, uh, you didn't have to go back to school?
本:你是说我学得太多,我毕业了?
Ben: You mean I learned so much I graduated?
麦琪:不,本.
Maggie: No Ben.I'm saying that you have done better in these two weeks
我是说你这两星期的学习比你在杜威中学学得还好.
than you have ever done at Dewey.
如果说留在家里上学,你觉得怎么样?
And how would you feel about just going to school here at home?
本:妈妈,这没有意思.
Ben: Mum, this isn't funny.
麦琪:本,我觉得你真的很喜欢读书的.
Maggie: Ben, I saw you actually excited about doing schoolwork.
我是说我们在一起很快活.
I mean you and I had fun together.
本:嘘!妈妈,如果我朋友听见你说的,他们会笑我的.当他们发现我进妈妈高中,他们会怎么做?
Ben: Shhhh.Mum if my friends heard you say that they'd laugh at me.You
know what they are going to do when they find out I'm going to Mummy
High
麦琪:亲爱的,我真的认为这是出于好意.
Maggie: Honey, I really think it's for the best.
我认为你心里也是这么想的.
And underneath I think you do too.
我是说,你要坦白的告诉我,
I mean can you honestly tell me,
你能真诚地说,
can you honestly say that you can hang out with Veto and the Coconut Boys
你能和沃特和敢死队四处闲逛,不会惹麻烦?
and not get into trouble?
本:我行……我一定行……这就是我刻苦学习了两个星期所得到的.
Ben: I certainly...I most certainly Carol...
更多的惩罚?
So this is what I get for my two weeks of hard work?More punishment?
麦琪:本,当你长大了,你会明白.
Maggie: Ben, when you're older you'll understand.
本:我不会长大.妈妈的孩子永远长不大.
Ben: I won't be getting any older.Mummy's boys have a short life span.
杰森:我看的出来他很好地接受了这个消息.
Jason: I see he took the news well.
麦琪:杰森,我坚信,在他的内心,他的灵魂最深,
Maggie: Jason, I firmly believe that underneath it, deep, deep,
最深,最深的地方,他知道这是出于好意.
deep within his soul, he knows this is for the best.
杰森:我不知道,麦琪.
Jason: I don't know Maggie.
我说,当我在他这么大的年纪,
I mean when I was his age,
只关心和小伙伴玩弹弓,
all I cared about was snapping towels with the guys and smelling bad and
闻臭味,还有对女孩子搞各种可笑的恶作剧.
getting all goofy and nervous around females.
麦琪:你小时候也是这样的?
Maggie: That happened when you were younger too?
杰森:已经没有必要打我了,麦琪.
Jason: There is no need to lash out at me Maggie.
麦琪:有,有必要.我觉得这点上你不支持我.
Maggie: Yes there is.I don't feel like I have your support in this.
杰森:亲爱的,听着,
Jason: Honey, look, all things considered, when you look at the options,
应该考虑所有方面,当你看着选项时,
I think that teaching Ben at home is worth a shot.
我觉得你在家里教本,
But if you want me to say that what you are doing is absolutely one hundred
是可以试一试.但是如果你要想我说,
percent, no doubt about it right.....
你做的绝对百分之一百的毫无疑问的正确……我不能这样说,除非你想要我撒谎.
I can't say that unless you want me to lie.
麦琪:会是个大大的谎言?
Maggie: Would it be a big lie?
麦琪:你怎么可以忘记洛杉矶是加利福尼亚州呢?
Maggie: How could you forget that Los Angeles is in California?
因为"你那里"的丁香肉串的联合总部就在那儿.
It is the corporate headquarters of Laylanni's loo al on a stick.
开萝尔:恩,妈妈.一句话.你伤心,是吗?
Carol: Um mother.A word.You hurt, don't you?
麦琪:没有.
Maggie: No.
开萝尔:妈妈,这是我.开萝尔,
Carol: Mum, this is me.Carol, your sensitive, perceptive daughter.
你敏感,善解人意的女儿.妈妈,
Mum, it's ok.I know hwy you are going through this pointless charade.
没关系.我知道你为何做这种无意义的看手势猜字谜游戏.弥补前几年造成的悲剧.
To make up for the tragedy of those lost years.But it's ok.
但是,没关系.愧疚使得女人远比有精神病要好.
Guilt has made women far better than you go insane.
克莉丝:听着,傻瓜.
Chrissy: Listen you rocks.
因为你,
Because of you she is going to want to try this on me.
她也想这样在我身上尝试.我的集体活动没了.
There goes my socialization.
本:嘿,瞧,
Ben: Hey look.I'm not too happy about this either.
又不是我想这样,我最不愿意待的地方就是这儿.
The last place I want to be is here.
克莉丝:那么你做点什么呀.从家逃走.
Chrissy: Then do something about it.Run away from home.
我为你收拾衣服.
I'll pack you're clothes for you.
麦琪:嗨,本,我希望你已经完成了今天你落下的所有作业,待在你的房间里,直到你全都记住了,否则你就跟西瓜一样烂.这也是个比喻,你可记住了.
Maggie: Hey Ben, I want to see everything you missed today covered in your homework
and you will stay in your room until you know it back and forwards or
you will rot like a bad melon.And that is a simile that you can
take to the man
德威特先生:西维尔太太,我隔着一个街区就听见你的声音了.
Mr.Dewitt: Mrs.Seaver, I could here you a block away.
你知道你会成为一个了不起的老师.
You know you would have made a great teacher?
麦琪:德威特先生,如果你来这儿是告诉我本需要社会活动,
Maggie: Mr.Dewitt, if you have come to tell me that Ben needs socialization,
或者他应该跟伙伴们出去闲荡,或者对姑娘恶作剧,
or that he needs to hang out with boys who snap towels or act goofy around
或者我这么做是出于内疚.
females, or that I am doing this only out of guilt: save it.
省省吧.我都听过了.
I have heard it all.
德威特先生:喂,喂,老师.
Mr.Dewitt: Here, here, teach.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
德威特先生:西维尔太太,我到这儿来是为你鼓掌的.
Mr.Dewitt: Mrs.Seaver, I have come here to applaud you.
这是我教育生涯中,第一次看见家长做了件正确的事.
For the first time in my career I have seen a parent do something right.
你控制了你儿子的生活,在他最需要的时候.
You took control of your son's life when he needed it most.
麦琪:喔,谢谢.就当我正在开始怀疑自己的时候.
Maggie: Wow, thanks.Just when I was beginning to doubt myself.
德威特先生:我所要说的是,
Mr.Dewitt: All I can say is I wish that all the parents of all the
我希望全世界所有的班级,所有的学生家长都能把孩子带回家去,
students in all the classrooms around the world,
教他们.
would take them home and teach them.
麦琪:但是你就会失业了.
Maggie: But the you'd be out of a job.
德威特先生:我是本地雇员.我哪也不去.
Mr.Dewitt: I'm a city employee.I aint going nowhere.
私下里告诉你,
On the QT, my mummy taught me at home for fourteen years and look how
我妈在家教了我14年,我现在成了什么样了?
I turned out.
本:啊,妈妈,
Ben: Uh mum, I'm too sick to stay at home today.
我今天对待在家里厌倦了.我得去学校.
I got to go to school.
麦琪:本,别……没什么,亲爱的.去吧.
Maggie: Ben, don't...it's ok honey.Go.
本:你不反对?
Ben: You re not arguing?
麦琪:不.在家里教你是个错误.
Maggie: No.It was a mistake teaching you at home.
对不起,我曾经陷入在家教你.
I'm sorry I ever got into it.
本:你怎么能这么说?行了,我学得不错,是吗?
Ben: How could you say that?Come on, I was doing good wasn't I?
麦琪:本,去上学.你要迟到了.
Maggie: Ben, just go to school.You're going to be late.
本:我不想去上学了.
Ben: I don't want to go to school.
麦琪:哦,那么你想待在家里?
Maggie: Oh so now you want o stay at home?
本:我也没这么说.
Ben: I didn't say that either.
麦琪:本,你只有两个选择.下决定吧.
Maggie: Ben those are your two choices.Make up your mind.
本:是呀,我知道.这都逼疯我了.
Ben: Yeah I know.It's driving me nuts.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What is?
本:妈妈,我喜欢跟你一起学习.
Ben: Mum, I like studying with you.And I actually learn something.
而且我真的学到了东西.如果每个人叫我笨蛋,这可不真的好听.
It's not real neat having everybody calling me stupid.
麦琪:有谁叫你笨蛋了?
Maggie: Who calls you stupid?
本:这是我的形象.这就是我所做的.这就是我.
Ben: It's my image.It's what I do.It's what I am.
麦琪:我不喜欢这个.
Maggie: I don't like that.
本:我也不喜欢.但是你知道,
Ben: I don't like it either.But you know, I'll tell y you what's worse.
我告诉你什么更糟糕,所有男孩叫我妈妈的宝贝儿子.
having all those guys calling me a mum's boy.
麦琪:谁这么说?
Maggie: Who's saying that?
本:他们全部,妈妈.
Ben: They all are mum.
当他们拖着球棒从栅栏前经过时,
When they walk by the house dragging the bat against the fence,
他们说这话.在夜里我听到汽车喇叭声,
they are saying it.
好像也在说我,
When I hear tires squeal late at night, it's meant for me mum.
妈妈.我真的不知道做什么,
I just don't know what to do mum.
妈妈.
I mean it's really neat having you all to myself.
我是说你只关心我一个人真不错.感到自己不笨真好.
Its really neat not feeling dumb.
麦琪:你真的喜欢和我在这?
Maggie: You did like being here with me?
本:嘘!他们随时都会露面.他们也许已经躲在树林里.
Ben: Shhh!They could show up at any time.They've been known to hide in bushes.
麦琪:那样你的麻烦太多了,年轻人.
Maggie: Well you are more trouble than you are worth young man.
本:啊!
Ben: Hu!
麦琪:你对于公立学校太危险,
Maggie: You are too dangerous for public school and you can just tell
你可以这样告诉你朋友我这么说的.
your friends I said so.
本:我不危险.
Ben: I'm not dangerous.
麦琪:对于这样的事情,他们就不会说,妈妈的宝贝儿子了,是吗?
Maggie: Such things wouldn't be said about a mum's boy, would they?
本:哦.那么我喜欢在这里上学,
Ben: Oh.So I could like go to school here and no one would have to
但是没有人会知道我真的喜欢在家里上学.
know that I am actually liking it?
麦琪:对,亲爱的.
Maggie: That's right honey.
本:亲爱的!
Ben: Honey!
麦琪:我说游手好闲.你太野而不能把你从放到路上.
Maggie: I mean dead beat.You are too wild to be let loose on the streets.
本:谢谢你.
Ben: Thank you.
麦琪:别客气.这可不是什么野餐,年轻人.
Maggie: You are welcome.This isn't going to be any picnic young man.
本:你仍然是在演戏,还是应该担心我.
Ben: Are we still acting or should I be worried.
本:妈妈,为什么你一定要去上班?
Ben: Mum, how come you had to go back to work?
麦琪:我不是不得不回去,本.我想去.
Maggie: I didn't have to go back to Ben.I wanted to.Come here.
过来.本,想想看,
Ben, imagine you had to spend fifteen years in this house without ever
如果你十五年一直是待在家里,从来不出去玩儿.你会发疯的,
going out to play.You'd go crazy wouldn't you?
是吗?请相信,许多人对于工作有相同的感受.
Well believe it or not, a lot of grown ups feel the same about work.
本:这是病态,妈妈.
Ben: That's sick mum.
麦琪:本,我知道这对我们是很大的变化.
Maggie: Ben I know this has been a big change for all of us.
而且我担心不和你待在这里,因为,这样,
And I worry about not being here for you because, well, you are the youngest.
因为你最小.另外我很担心开萝尔,
And I worry about not being here for Carol because she's a girl and she
因为她是个女孩,她需要母亲.我当然也很担心迈克,
needs her mother.And I worry about not being here for Mike,
因为他时常要闯点祸.还有,
to stop him from accidentally blowing something up.
相信我,我更担心让你爸一个人对付你们这些怪物.
And believe me, I worry about leaving your father here to cope with all
本:你不应该这么担心,妈妈.这样你会使自己发疯的.
you monsters. Ben: You shouldn't worry so much Mum,
00:22:28,000
You'll make yourself crazy.